<page>
 <h1>
  Wrench
 </h1>
 <h3>
  Source
 </h3>
 <text><style color="0xaaaaaa" italic="true">Note: this page is ported from MCMOD's GTCEu wiki.<br/>Author: <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/179043/">花海</style>, <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/119280/">Oganesson897</style>, <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="TacoMonkey's Github" underlined="true" url-link="https://github.com/TacoMonkey11">TacoMonkey</style><br/></style></text>
 <text>
  When right-clicking the wrench on a machine:
 </text>
 <br/>
 <text left-margin="10">
  • Whilst standing:
   If you aim at any side of the machine, you can adjust the active output direction of the machine (i.e. the side with the black square) to the corresponding side (the front side cannot be set as the output direction). The output direction may also be adjusted using the machine GUI.
  <br/>
  <br/>
  • Whilst crouching:
   You can rotate the machine depending on the side you click.
     Each time the above operation is performed, the wrench will consume 1 durability point (Creative mode causes no durability to be lost). A wrench with a durability of 0 will be no longer be able to rotate or change the output side of a machine (Bug).
  <br/>
 </text>
 <text> Similarly to the <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:tools/wire_cutter" underlined="true">wire cutter</style>, wrenches may also be used to interact with placed item/fluid pipes. You can connect or disconnect pipes from machines and other pipes.</text>
 <text>
  <br/>
   Wrenches can also be used as a crafting tool. Wrenches are required to craft machine casings, power tools, frames and other items. You can view all usages of the wrench by using a recipe browser.
 </text>
 <br/>

 <recipe id="gtceu:shaped/wrench_iron"/>
 <br/>
 <text isCenter="true">This is just one example of a recipe, wrenches can be crafted using most GregTech materials.</text>
</page>
