<page>
 <h1>
  Ultimate Battery
 </h1>
 <h3>
  Source
 </h3>
 <text><style color="0xaaaaaa" italic="true">Note: this page is ported from MCMOD's GTCEu wiki.<br/>Author: <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/179043/">花海</style><br/></style></text>
 <h2 font-color="0xff0000">
  WARNING!!!
 </h2>
 <text isCenter="true">
  <style color="0xff0000">The warning means this is not a reliable page.</style>
  <br/>
  <style bold="true" color="0xffaa00">Please do not report any mistakes on the page, either discord or github.</style>
  <br/>
  This page is translated from the Chinese wiki which hasn't been reviewed and polished yet. It may contain errors and inaccuracies. We are looking forward to your help by improving this page.
 </text>
 <text>
  <br/>
  <style>
   <style color="0xaaaaaa" italic="true">"Fill it to beat Minecraft"</style>
   <br/>
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   The Ultimate Battery is a UHV voltage-rated battery that can store a maximum of 9,223,372,036,854,775,807 EU (2
 -1 EU) of energy and can last approximately 61,083,979 hours (4,398,046,511,104 ticks) at full energy.
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   The raw materials for the synthesis of the ultimate battery are complex, requiring the use of metallic eutectic materials, neutron materials, and silica-enriched ternary europium, tin, and uranium alloy materials,
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Wetware computer host</style>
   (UHV level circuit),
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">
 Rock Salt - RockSalt
</style>
   , polybenzimidazole (PBI), super silica and other late-game raw materials are available at
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">
 (default value 
 (30, 30, 30)): The system sets the background color of the drop-down list for the Home key click action; 
</style>
   Made in 
, synthesis requires UV-level voltage.
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   The inner material of the ultimate battery that has just been synthesized appears red, and will gradually turn green as the stored energy increases.
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   Obtaining the Ultimate Battery for the first time will complete the challenge "What Now?" (Description: Make an Ultimate Battery).
   <br/>
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
</page>
