<page>
 <h1>
  Assembling Machine
 </h1>
 <h3>
  Source
 </h3>
 <text><style color="0xaaaaaa" italic="true">Note: this page is ported from MCMOD's GTCEu wiki.<br/>Author: <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/179043/">花海</style>, <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/119280/">Oganesson897</style>, <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/2/">重生是希望</style><br/></style></text>
 <h2 font-color="0xff0000">
  WARNING!!!
 </h2>
 <text isCenter="true">
  <style color="0xff0000">The warning means this is not a reliable page.</style>
  <br/>
  <style bold="true" color="0xffaa00">Please do not report any mistakes on the page, either discord or github.</style>
  <br/>
  This page is translated from the Chinese wiki which hasn't been reviewed and polished yet. It may contain errors and inaccuracies. We are looking forward to your help by improving this page.
 </text>
 <text>
  <br/>
  <style>
   <style color="0xaaaaaa" italic="true">"Avengers Assemble!"/"Not a Workbench"/"Assembly Constructor"</style>
   <br/>
   The picture above shows the initial interface of the terminal, which is similar to an iPad graphic.
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   The assembly machine can be understood as an electric workbench, but the items it can manufacture are more diverse. It comes with 9 item input slots and 1 fluid input slot, with LV, MV and HV voltages and above. The fluid reserves of the three levels of assembly machines are 8,000 L, 12,000 L and 16,000 L respectively. It is mainly capable of performing the following compositions:
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
 <text left-margin="10">
  •
  <style>
   many in the original
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">workbench</style>
   Items that can be crafted in 
. The amount of raw materials required for synthesis is basically the same, and some of the original materials will be replaced with corresponding fluid forms to participate in assembly. Typical examples:
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
 <text left-margin="20">
  •
  <style>
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">
 Stainless Steel - StainlessSteel
</style>
   . The same amount of items required to craft directly in the workbench, assembly requires 7
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Glass</style>
   was replaced with 1,008 mB molten glass.
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  •
  <style>
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">
 upgraded to 
</style>
   . GTCEu has modified and covered the synthesis table of the hopper in the original version. In addition to consuming 5 iron plates and 1 box in the workbench, it also requires 1 small iron gear and
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">wrench</style>
   and
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">forging hammer</style>
   Capable of storing 8,000 L and 16,000 L respectively. EV and above gas turbines are replaced by multi-block machines
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
 <text left-margin="10">
  •
  <style>
   Various mechanical components, including but not limited to LV ~ IV level
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">electric motor</style>
   and other basic components of the machine;
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">transistor</style>
   The structure body of 
.
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">
 Rhodium-plated palladium alloy ingot - RhodiumPlatedPalladium
</style>
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">resistance</style>
   , as well as the corresponding patch forms and advanced patch forms, etc.;
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  •
  <style>
   Use corresponding plastic material foils to make wires of different voltage levels and materials into cables;
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  •
  <style>
   Samarium - Samarium
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">QuarkTech™ Suite</style>
   Wait.
   <br/>
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
 <text>
  <br/>
  <style>
   Note: The assembly machine cannot be used to assemble circuits. LV ~ IV level circuits need to be
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">
 Sterling Silver - SterlingSilver - CuAg4
</style>
   Assembled in 
, please pay attention to distinguish the functional differences between the two; most circuits, mechanical components and other items with LuV ~ UV levels need to be assembled in
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">assembly line</style>
   can only be obtained by assembling it in medium. The assembly line can be thought of as a more advanced assembler, but it is not compatible with the recipes that a single block assembler can handle.
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
</page>
