<page>
    <h1>Arc Furnace</h1>
    <text>
        The assembly machine can be understood as an electric workbench, but it can produce more diverse items, with 9 item input tanks and 1 fluid input tank, LV, MV and HV and above the assembly fluid reserves of 8,000 L, 12,000 L and 16,000 L respectively. It is mainly capable of performing the following compositions:
        <br/>
        <br/>
        • Many items that can be synthesized in the original workbench. The amount of raw material required for synthesis is basically the same, and some of the original material will be replaced with the corresponding fluid form to participate in the assembly. Typical examples are:
        <br/>
        <style>  </style> - Ender Crystal. The seven glasses required for assembly were replaced with 1,008 mB of molten glass, the same amount of material required for direct synthesis in the workbench.
        <br/>
        <style>  </style> - Hopper. GTCEu modified and covered the composition table of the funnel in the original version. In addition to consuming 5 iron plates and 1 box in the workbench, it also needed a small iron gear and was made with a <style color="0xafff00" underlined="true" link="gtceu:tools/wrench" hover-info="click link">wrench</style> and a <style color="0xafff00" underlined="true" link="gtceu:tools/hammer" hover-info="click link">hammer</style>. In the assembly machine, there is no need to consume excess small iron gears, and other tools are no longer needed to assist in the synthesis.
        <br/>
        This type of recipes usually requires only ULV-level voltage to perform.

        <br/>
        <br/>
        • Various components, including but not limited to LV ~ IV electric motors and other basic components of the machine; Transistors, diodes, capacitors and resistors, and corresponding patch shapes and advanced patch shapes, etc.;

        <br/>
        <br/>
        • Use the corresponding plastic material foil to make wires of different voltage levels and materials into cables;

        <br/>
        <br/>
        • Other piecemeal compositions, such as for assembling coil blocks and QuarkTech™ sets, etc.

        <br/>
        <br/>
        <style italic="true">Note: Assembly machines cannot be used to assemble circuits. LV ~ IV circuit needs to be assembled in the circuit assembly machine, please pay attention to distinguish the difference between the two functions; Most of the circuits, mechanical components and other items from the LuV ~ UV grade need to be assembled in the assembly line to be produced. The assembly line can be understood as a higher level assembly machine, but it is not compatible with the formula that a single block assembly machine can handle.</style>
    </text>
</page>