<page>
 <h1>
  Electromagnetic Separator
 </h1>
 <h3>
  Source
 </h3>
 <text><style color="0xaaaaaa" italic="true">Note: this page is ported from MCMOD's GTCEu wiki.<br/>Author: <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/179043/">花海</style>, <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/119280/">Oganesson897</style>, <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/2/">重生是希望</style><br/></style></text>
 <h2 font-color="0xff0000">
  WARNING!!!
 </h2>
 <text isCenter="true">
  <style color="0xff0000">The warning means this is not a reliable page.</style>
  <br/>
  <style bold="true" color="0xffaa00">Please do not report any mistakes on the page, either discord or github.</style>
  <br/>
  This page is translated from the Chinese wiki which hasn't been reviewed and polished yet. It may contain errors and inaccuracies. We are looking forward to your help by improving this page.
 </text>
 <text>
  <br/>
  <style>
   <style color="0xaaaaaa" italic="true">"Separate magnetic ores from other ores"/"Electromagnetic classifier"/"Electromagnetic field remover"</style>
   <br/>
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   Electromagnetic concentrator can separate different products from clean powder. Cleansing powders capable of processing often contain magnetic ingredients, including iron, neodymium, gold and enriched silica. All cleansing powders that can be processed are as follows:
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
 <text left-margin="10">
  •
  <style>
   , polybenzimidazole (PBI), super silica and other late-game raw materials are available at
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Iron particles</style>
   and Xiaodui Iron Fan;
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  •
  <style>
   Clean fluorocarbon lanthanum cerite powder and monazite powder. Able to separate small piles of neodymium powder as by-products;
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  •
  <style>
   Clean magnetite powder (clean vanadium magnetite powder), granite ore sand and basalt ore sand. Able to separate
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">gold nuggets</style>
   Phosphorus Pentoxide - PhosphorusPentoxide
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  •
  <style>
   Clean silica powder. Small piles of enriched silica powder can be separated, which can also be used as a way to extract more enriched silica from silica ores.
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
 <text>
  <br/>
  <style>
   As one of the synthetic materials of other basic components of the same voltage level, such as
   <br/>
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
</page>
