<page>
 <h1>
  Wiremill
 </h1>
 <h3>
  Source
 </h3>
 <text><style color="0xaaaaaa" italic="true">Note: this page is ported from MCMOD's GTCEu wiki.<br/>Author: <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/179043/">花海</style>, <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/119280/">Oganesson897</style>, <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/2/">重生是希望</style><br/></style></text>
 <h2 font-color="0xff0000">
  WARNING!!!
 </h2>
 <text isCenter="true">
  <style color="0xff0000">The warning means this is not a reliable page.</style>
  <br/>
  <style bold="true" color="0xffaa00">Please do not report any mistakes on the page, either discord or github.</style>
  <br/>
  This page is translated from the Chinese wiki which hasn't been reviewed and polished yet. It may contain errors and inaccuracies. We are looking forward to your help by improving this page.
 </text>
 <text>
  <br/>
  <style>
   A wire rod rolling mill is a machine used to manufacture
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Cable</style>
   and
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Thin wire</style>
   ’s machine.
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   It can process 1 ingot into 2 wires of the corresponding material, and 1 wire into 4 thin wires of the corresponding material. All materials processed require only LV level voltage to operate.
   <br/>
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
 <text left-margin="10">
  •
  <style>
   If this material does not have a corresponding wire form (such as borosilicate glass strips), 1 ingot can be directly processed into 8 thin wires of the corresponding material;
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  •
  <style>
   If this material does not have a corresponding ingot form, but there is a corresponding powder and wire form (such as graphene powder), you can directly use 1 powder to process it into 2 wires of the corresponding material.
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
 <text>
  <br/>
  <style>
   The wire rod mill can also process a single polycaprolactam strip into 32
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Wire</style>
   Niobium Titanium Alloy - NiobiumTitanium - NbTi - 296
   <br/>
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
</page>
