<page>
  <h1>Tool Heads And Turbine Blade</h1>
  <h3>Source</h3>
  <text>
    <style color="0xaaaaaa" italic="true">Author: <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://github.com/blackdragon2447">BlackDragon2447</style></style>
  </text>
  <h2>Tool Heads</h2>
  <text>Electric tools (Which are currently not yet implemented) have replaceable heads, the stats of an electric tool are not only dependent on the <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:misc/power_unit" underlined="true">Power Unit</style> but also on the head. Electric tools, and thus their heads come in 5 flavours, but the gist for all of them is the same: the mining level and durability of the tool are determined by the material their head is made out of. The advantage of using electric tools is that their heads are replaceable and thus a head can be transfered when you want to upgrade the power unit and you don't need a new power unit when you want to upgrade or break the head.</text>
  <!-- <text> -->
  <!--   <style color="0xcc8932">Tool stat comparison comming once electric tools are implemented.</style> -->
  <!-- </text> -->
  <h3>Crafting</h3>
  <text>All tool heads need to be crafted manually, with exeception of the buzzsaw blade, which can in some cases be crafted in the <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:machines/lathe" underlined="true">Lathe</style> from a gear. The steel parts of the recipe are independent of the material you want to make the tool head out of and are always there.</text>
  <recipe id="gtceu:shaped/drill_head_aluminium"></recipe>
  <recipe id="gtceu:shaped/chainsaw_head_aluminium"></recipe>
  <recipe id="gtceu:shaped/buzzsaw_blade_aluminium"></recipe>
  <recipe id="gtceu:lathe/buzzsaw_gear_aluminium"></recipe>
  <recipe id="gtceu:shaped/wrench_head_aluminium"></recipe>
  <recipe id="gtceu:shaped/screwdriver_tip_aluminium"></recipe>
  <h2>Turbine Blade</h2>
	Turbine blades are to turbines what tool heads are to electric tools, turbine blades determine a turbines Durability, Efficiency and Power.
	<h3>Crafting</h3>
	<text>Turbine blades can be crafted both manually and using a <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:machines/forming_press" underlined="true">Forming Press</style></text>
  <recipe id="gtceu:shaped/turbine_blade_aluminium"></recipe>
  <recipe id="gtceu:forming_press/press_aluminium_turbine_rotor"></recipe>
</page>
