<page>
  <h1>Wire and Cable</h1>
  <h3>Source</h3>
  <text>
    <style color="0xaaaaaa" italic="true">Note: this page is ported from MCMOD's GTCEu wiki. <br></br>Author: <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/119280/">Oganesson897</style>, <br></br> <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://github.com/blackdragon2447">BlackDragon2447</style> <br></br></style>
  </text>
  <text>Wires and cables are used to transport power, with cables being the generally more convenient option, at the cost of needing to be insulated. (Everything said after this point about wires also holds for cables unless otherwise stated). A wire's voltage and loss are determined by the material while the amperage is (in general), determined by the size of the wire (1x, 2x, 4x, 8x or 16x). A wire's tooltip will indicate the wire's amperage, voltage and loss. The voltage of a wire indicates the max EU/t a machine is able to draw for each amp it draws. For example: take a <style color="0xbbffaa">2x Electrum Wire</style>, that wire is able to transport 4A of HV (4 * 512 EU/t), a machine trying to draw 1A of EV (2048 EU/t) is only able to draw 512 EU/t since it only draws 1 amp and the wire's voltage is HV (512 EU/t), at the same time, an <style color="0xbbffaa">HV Energy Hatch</style> is able to draw 1024 EU/t from the same wire since it is drawing 2 amps (2 * 512 EU/t). If a wire's max amperage is exceeded, the wires will burn and set fire the the block they occupied, for example: Having 5 1A generators AND 5 machines drawing power on a 4A line (Trying to draw more amps than the wire is rated for without the matching input or vice versa will not burn the wire). Wires and cables (with the exeption of superconductors) have a passive loss. Loss is measured in EU per meter per amp, for example: <style color="0xbbffaa">2x Electrum Wire</style> has a loss of 4 EU/Meter/Amp, this means that if you have a generator generating 2 amps of HV (1024 EU/t) and a machine 3 cables/meters away drawing 2 amps, the loss is 4 * 3 * 2 = 24 EU, in other words, the machine receives 1000 EU/t. A wire's loss can be reduced by insulating, any non superconductor wire that isn't insulated will electrocute the player if they touch the wire.</text>
  <h3>Crafting</h3>
  <text>Wires are crafted manually using a wirecutter and a <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:materials/plate" underlined="true">Plate</style>, or, for a better ratio, in a <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:machines/wiremill" underlined="true">Wiremill</style>, <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:machines/extruder" underlined="true">Extruder</style>.</text>
  <recipe id="gtceu:shaped/aluminium_wire_single"></recipe>
  <recipe id="gtceu:wiremill/mill_aliminium_wire"></recipe>
  <recipe id="gtceu:extruder/extrude_aluminium_wire"></recipe>
  <h3>Insulating</h3>
  <text>Insulating is done using in an <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:machines/assembler" underlined="true">Assembler</style> any type of rubber, needing less rubber for the more advanced types of rubber (4:2:1 Rubber:Silicone Rubber:Styrene Butadiene Rubber (Wires after EV cannot be insulated using normal Rubber)) and, depending on the tier of the wire, either only <style color="0xbbffaa">Thin Polyvinyl Chloride Sheets</style> or <style color="0xbbffaa">Thin Polyvinyl Chloride Sheets</style> and <style color="0xbbffaa">Thin Polypenylene Sulfide Sheets</style> (Superconductors cannot be insulated).</text>
  <recipe id="gtceu:assembler/cover_copper_wire_gt_single_rubber"></recipe>
  <recipe id="gtceu:assembler/cover_aluminium_wire_gt_single_rubber"></recipe>
  <recipe id="gtceu:assembler/cover_osmium_wire_gt_single_silicone"></recipe>
</page>
