<page>
 <h1>
  Fertilizer
 </h1>
 <h3>
  Source
 </h3>
 <text><style color="0xaaaaaa" italic="true">Note: this page is ported from MCMOD's GTCEu wiki.<br/>Author: <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/179043/">花海</style>, <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/508290/">morningglory</style><br/></style></text>
 <h2 font-color="0xff0000">
  WARNING!!!
 </h2>
 <text isCenter="true">
  <style color="0xff0000">The warning means this is not a reliable page.</style>
  <br/>
  <style bold="true" color="0xffaa00">Please do not report any mistakes on the page, either discord or github.</style>
  <br/>
  This page is translated from the Chinese wiki which hasn't been reviewed and polished yet. It may contain errors and inaccuracies. We are looking forward to your help by improving this page.
 </text>
 <text>
  <br/>
  <style>
   Cut 1 log of any variety into 6 planks of the corresponding variety, and produce 2 wood pulp at the same time. If 3 wooden boards of this type can be combined into steps in a workbench, then 2 wooden boards of this type can also be further processed into 2 of this type of steps.
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
 <text left-margin="10">
  •
  <style>
   By
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">
 Etched Lambton chip by 
</style>
   ,
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">
 Rhodium - Rhodium
</style>
   Plutonium 239 - Plutonium
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">
 Ruthenium
</style>
   Plutonium 241 - Plutonium241
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">mixer</style>
   Advanced large diesel engine
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  •
  <style>
   Polyimide Kapton-K - Kapton K
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">
 to make 8 ingots into 1 
</style>
   (or
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">
 (50% material waste). If the material has a melting point of 2,800 K and above, a minimum MV level voltage (60 EU/t) is required to perform, otherwise only an LV level voltage (14 EU/t) is required. The processing time without overclocking is 10 times the average mass of the material; 
</style>
   ) is isolated as a solid product. The distillation chamber requires MV level voltage (45 EU/t), and the distillation column requires HV level voltage (180 EU/t);
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  •
  <style>
   at
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Chemical reactor</style>
   It is produced by reacting calcite powder, glauconite ore, apatite powder, ash (black ash), sulfur powder, phosphate powder and other raw materials as raw materials. Requires LV class voltage (30 EU/t) for operation.
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
 <text>
  <br/>
  <style>
   The effect of fertilizer is the same as the original
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">bone meal</style>
   Data that cannot be stored, such as 
 is required
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">use</style>
   The 
 key (default is the right mouse button) will ripen it.
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
</page>
