<page>
    <h1>
        Basic Arc Furnace
    </h1>
    <text>
        <style color="0xffaaaaaa" italic="true">"Who needs a blast furnace?"</style>
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <style>The arc furnace is similar to a power consumption</style>
        <style color="0xffafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Soil high furnace</style>
        <style>It can separate various tools, components, machines and other items into different materials with oxygen, so it is usually used in the recycling processing of such objects.There are some special cases at the same time:</style>
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <style>
        </style>
        •
        <style>If the processing items contain wooden (including</style>
        <style color="0xffafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Book</style>
        <style>and</style>
        <style color="0xffafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Paper</style>
        <style>Or or plastic components (including different types of rubber, epoxy resin, polyethylene, polyphenylene pyramole, etc.), it will be converted into ashes during the output;</style>
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <style>
        </style>
        •
        <style>If the processed items contain iron or copper components, it will be converted into forging iron (annealing copper) during the output.This is also one of the important sources of forging iron (annealing copper);</style>
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <style>
        </style>
        •
        <style>If the processed items contain diamonds, it will be converted into carbon powder at the time of output;</style>
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <style>
        </style>
        •
        <style>If the processed items contain magnetic ingredients, it will be demagnetized during the output;</style>
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <style>
        </style>
        •
        <style>Arbitrary</style>
        <style color="0xffafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Glass</style>
        <style>After the arc furnace is treated, it will be obtained</style>
        <style color="0xffafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Tempered glass</style>
        <style>Essenceexist</style>
        <style color="0xffafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Power blast</style>
        <style>Mid -processing glass can also be strengthened, but compared to the former, the consumption and oxygen consumption is greater.</style>
        <br/>
    </text>
</page>