<page>
 <h1>
  Block Breaker
 </h1>
 <h3>
  Source
 </h3>
 <text><style color="0xaaaaaa" italic="true">Note: this page is ported from MCMOD's GTCEu wiki.<br/>Author: <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/179043/">花海</style>, <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/2/">重生是希望</style><br/></style></text>
 <h2 font-color="0xff0000">
  WARNING!!!
 </h2>
 <text isCenter="true">
  <style color="0xff0000">The warning means this is not a reliable page.</style>
  <br/>
  <style bold="true" color="0xffaa00">Please do not report any mistakes on the page, either discord or github.</style>
  <br/>
  This page is translated from the Chinese wiki which hasn't been reviewed and polished yet. It may contain errors and inaccuracies. We are looking forward to your help by improving this page.
 </text>
 <text>
  <br/>
  <style>
   <style color="0xaaaaaa" italic="true">"Dig the block ahead and collect the drops"</style>
   <br/>
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   The upgraded version of 
 is faster than the former.
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   Brass - Brass
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">
 Nickel chromium alloy - Nichrome
</style>
   coke oven bricks
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">electric motor</style>
   , 2 
 of corresponding voltage levels
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">1x cable</style>
   , 2 circuits with corresponding voltage levels, 1
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">box</style>
   (
 is available
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">trap chest</style>
   and any item containing the mineral dictionary chestWood instead), and 1
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Diamond grinding head</style>
   .
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">
 One of the functional blocks of the multi-block structure. 
</style>
   owns
   <br/>
   2 × 2 output item cache, a single mining consumes 32 EU energy, and there is no speed bonus. Each time the voltage level of the block breaker increases, the speed bonus increases
   <br/>
   20% (the speed bonus will not exceed 90% under any circumstances), the energy consumed in a single mining operation will also be increased to 4 times that of the previous level, the maximum number of item caches will also be increased, and the voltage level is MV ~
   <br/>
   EV level block breakers have cache sizes of 3 × 3, 4 × 4 and 5 × 5 respectively.
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   The block breaker will only work when activated by a redstone signal, and will mine the nearest block it is facing while working. If the block is air, the mining will be skipped. The number of time ticks required to mine a block is ⌈⌈block hardness × 5⌉ × (1 - speed bonus)⌉. Block breakers cannot break blocks with a hardness of 0 or negative.
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   After the block is destroyed, the block breaker will automatically collect its dropped items and store them in its own item cache. If the cache is full, the dropped items will be left in the world. Block breaker every 5
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">game moment</style>
   will try to transfer the contents of the cache to an adjacent container through the output port.
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
</page>
