<page>
 <h1>
  Bio Chaff
 </h1>
 <h3>
  Source
 </h3>
 <text><style color="0xaaaaaa" italic="true">Note: this page is ported from MCMOD's GTCEu wiki.<br/>Author: <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/179043/">花海</style>, <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/119280/">Oganesson897</style><br/></style></text>
 <h2 font-color="0xff0000">
  WARNING!!!
 </h2>
 <text isCenter="true">
  <style color="0xff0000">The warning means this is not a reliable page.</style>
  <br/>
  <style bold="true" color="0xffaa00">Please do not report any mistakes on the page, either discord or github.</style>
  <br/>
  This page is translated from the Chinese wiki which hasn't been reviewed and polished yet. It may contain errors and inaccuracies. We are looking forward to your help by improving this page.
 </text>
 <text>
  <br/>
  <style>
   @ n @ biological bran by @ n @
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Botanical Balls</style>
   @ n @ at @ n @
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">lapping machine</style>
   @ n @ can be obtained by treatment at ULV voltage level, and 2 plant balls can be crushed to produce 2 ~ 4 biological bran. @ n @
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   @ n @ Biological bran can be further crushed in the mill to obtain @ n @
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">dirt</style>
   @ n @. At @ n @
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Pyrolysis furn</style>
   @ n @ can also be re-produced in an autoclave with molten europium, fungus mud, or mutagen as a complete crystal chip feedstock, with a higher yield probability (80%) of the finished product. @ n @
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Water</style>
   @ n @ Mixing and heating can produce substances or fermented biomass, and the type of product is determined by the programming circuit configuration values provided. Biological bran is also one of the main raw materials for the preparation of bacteria, at @ n @
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">@ n @ Argon Plasma - Plasma Argon @ n @</style>
   @ n @ is made by mixing with distilled water in a sterile ultra-pure room environment, and the reaction requires an HV-level voltage. @ n @
   <br/>
   N
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   @ n @ at @ n @
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Furnace</style>
   In @ n @, biological bran can be used as a fuel with a burning time of 200 t (burning 1 item). @ n @
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
</page>
