<page>
 <h1>
  Raw Crystal Chip
 </h1>
 <h3>
  Source
 </h3>
 <text><style color="0xaaaaaa" italic="true">Note: this page is ported from MCMOD's GTCEu wiki.<br/>Author: <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/179043/">花海</style>, <style color="0xa4e7ff" hover-info="url" underlined="true" url-link="https://center.mcmod.cn/508290/">morningglory</style><br/></style></text>
 <h2 font-color="0xff0000">
  WARNING!!!
 </h2>
 <text isCenter="true">
  <style color="0xff0000">The warning means this is not a reliable page.</style>
  <br/>
  <style bold="true" color="0xffaa00">Please do not report any mistakes on the page, either discord or github.</style>
  <br/>
  This page is translated from the Chinese wiki which hasn't been reviewed and polished yet. It may contain errors and inaccuracies. We are looking forward to your help by improving this page.
 </text>
 <text>
  <br/>
  <style>
   @ n @ Raw materials for crystal chips are essential for making crystal processors in the extreme differential pressure phase. @ n @
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   @ n @ crystalline chip raw materials need to be produced in @ n @
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Ultra-clean room</style>
   @ n @ Conducted in the environment by exquisite emeralds or exquisite olivines at @ n @
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Autoclave</style>
   Europium treatment with 16L molten state in @ n @ is made with a small probability (10%), which requires HV level voltage for operation, but using higher level voltage level processing can greatly increase the production probability. @ n @
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   N
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Part of the crystal chip raw material</style>
   @ n @ can also be re-produced in an autoclave with molten europium, fungus mud, or mutagen as a complete crystal chip feedstock, with a higher yield probability (80%) of the finished product. @ n @
  </style>
  <br/>
  <br/>
  <style>
   @ n @ crystal chip raw materials are mainly located in @ n @
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Electric blast furnace</style>
   Used in @ n @ for production @ n @
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">Etched Crystal Chip</style>
   @ n @, also available at @ n @
   <style color="0xafff00" hover-info="click link" link="gtceu:links" underlined="true">forging hammer</style>
   @ n @ is re-decomposed into a part of the crystal chip raw material, which is used to follow the above process to increase production. @ n @
  </style>
  <br/>
 </text>
</page>
